♪
[SHIMIZU AKARI]
Huh?
[blood splashing]
[thuds]
[gasps]
Don't let your guard down!
Something's here!
[FUJISHIMA TATSUMI]
Obviously!
Hold still, you piece of...
[FUJISHIMA TATSUMI]
Kenzo!
[gasps]
♪
[running footsteps]
[FUJISHIMA TATSUMI]
I've got you!
[sword clanking]
♪
[blood splashing]
[squealing]
[grunts]
[MA DONGWOOK] These insects
are in the same league
as S-ranks!
Uh!
[growls]
But they're still
just magic beasts!
No finesse, no real strategy.
Against the versatile tactics
we bring to a battle.
They can't win!
♪
[blood splashing]
[thuds]
[sighs]
The ants down here
are surprisingly durable.
Yeah.
It's a good thing there
weren't too many of them.
[MIN BYUNG-GU] It's not like
it would've mattered anyway.
Don't forget,
you got me backing you up.
So, you can relax!
That's some big talk for a guy
who was almost
too scared to join us.
[MIN BYUNG-GU]
Give it a rest, Yoonho.
What is this?
Your first raid?
You're getting sloppy.
These ants
don't go down that easy.
Even without their heads
they can still move.
You really oughta be
dismembering them, too.
Oh, yeah.
[blood splatters]
The further we go,
the stronger they get,
but we still haven't seen
any of those biped ants.
If I had to guess, these came
from a previous generation
of queen's guards
that were made obsolete.
So, they were just
the opening act, huh?
Are we sure
we're on the right path?
We're going the right way.
I think.
[BAEK YOONHO]
What?
I wouldn't worry.
There's something up ahead.
I can smell a powerful
magic-beast further within.
If we've gotten close enough
for you to smell them,
then President Baek should
be able to find them, right?
[scoffs]
Fine.
♪
There she is!
The queen's waiting for us
in the deepest chamber.
Looks like she's got
plenty of protection.
Guess there was a limit
on how many ants
the diversionary force
could lure away.
Her personal guards
are there too,
each of them
as strong as an S-rank.
Unfortunately, I couldn't tell
how strong the queen is.
It'll be a tough fight.
But with this lineup,
I know we can win!
Let's go!
[TOGETHER]
Right!
[running footsteps]
[groans]
[IZAWA IPPEI]
We're here.
This is Team Charlie's
last known location
before they went dark.
[KEI] Where the hell
could they have gone?
[IZAWA IPPEI] Doesn't look like
they had trouble
killing the ants.
[gasps]
Fujishima's glasses.
No way!
[trembling]
[Kei grunts]
-[Kei coughing]
-[IZAWA IPPEI] What's wrong?
[KEI]
This stench.
It's beyond revolting.
[groans]
I've never smelled
anything like it before!
[gasps]
[screaming]
[rumbling]
[shattering]
[running footsteps]
[KUMAMOTO ATSUSHI]
Any luck reaching Team Charlie?
[TAWATA KANAE]
They haven't responded yet.
[KUMAMOTO ATSUSHI] Wonder if
something happened to them.
[TAWATA KANAE] This isn't
the time to worry about that!
You gonna actually
fight this time?
[KUMAMOTO ATSUSHI]
I guess if I have to.
♪
[CHOI JONG-IN]
Well, well.
They're rolling out
the red carpet for us.
♪
We wouldn't wanna be rude,
let's respond to their
hospitality in kind.
[all gasp]
[smirks]
Remember to stick
to the plan, people!
I'll make space for
Mister Ultimate Weapon here
to light 'em all up.
[CHOI JONG-IN]
Yes, we know what to do.
[MA DONGWOOK] You ants
are gonna have to get past me!
Ugh!
[grunts]
♪
[fire crackling]
[rumbling]
[CHOI JONG-IN]
It's been a long time
since I've had to use
this kind of firepower.
But I can't afford
to hold anything back
with so much on the line.
Hm!
♪
[explosion]
[squealing]
[BAEK YOONHO]
He's right.
There's no reason
to hold anything back.
It doesn't matter
how ugly it might get.
I'm going slaughter
these monsters,
down to the last filthy bug!
[growls]
[roars]
♪
[panting]
[CHA HAE-IN]
There it is.
[roars]
[CHA HAE-IN] President Baek's
transformation.
♪
[CAMERAMAN 22A]
It's started.
[PRODUCER 23A]
We've got over 80% viewership!
See if you can get
a better angle!
[CAMERAMAN 22A] There are
that many people watching this?
I don't want to let them down.
[gasps]
Huh?
We're inside the boss room
of an S-rank dungeon.
Are you trying to die?
Uh, no, just trying
to get a better look, sir.
Do me a favor and stand back.
It's going to get
even more intense.
♪
[NEWSCASTER 3A]
This is it!
The S-rank hunters have finally
reached the queen ant's lair
and are, at this moment,
engaging in a life
and death battle
to liberate Jeju Island.
We've got hunters
from multiple guilds
who never operate together,
but as you can see,
they're using
incredible teamwork
to face this threat.
[squeaking]
♪
[groans]
[roars]
[explosion]
[growls]
[rumbling]
♪
[thuds]
[squealing]
[growls]
♪
Uh!
[fire crackling]
♪
Hm!
[sword clanking]
[NEWSCASTER 3A]
Hunter Cha's razor-sharp attack
slices through another one!
It's down!
The last royal guard
ant has fallen!
[panting]
[squeaking]
[Ma Dongwook grunts]
[MA DONGWOOK]
It's just her.
Let's finish this!
[grunts]
She's as good as done now!
♪
Without her guards,
the queen's nothing more
than a giant punching bag!
Uh!
[squealing]
♪
[groans]
[grunting]
[gasps]
♪
If that bug wants you
out of this fight,
she's gonna have
to get rid of me first!
♪
[Ma Dongwook grunts]
[MA DONGWOOK]
You're dreaming if you think
you can get close
to our healer!
[CHOI JONG-IN] That's it!
Keep her occupied for me.
Uh-ugh!
[squealing]
Uh!
♪
[rumbling]
[squealing]
[MA DONGWOOK]
I can't believe she's still got
this much strength left.
♪
[BAEK YOONHO]
Was that a death cry?
Or something else?
[squealing]
-Take this!
-We've got you!
[squealing]
[Ma Dongwook grunts]
-Now, Hunter Cha!
-Your turn, Miss Cha!
On it!
One last push!
♪
[sword clanking]
[thuds]
♪
[yelling]
[panting]
♪
[thuds]
[sighs]
♪
[cheering]
[NEWSCASTER 3A]
They've done it!
[crowd cheering]
Chairman!
[sighs]
Mission accomplished,
at long last.
[CHA HAE-IN]
It's over now.
Right?
[LIM TAE-GYU]
Seems like it.
With the queen dead,
the surviving ants
will die out within a year.
[MA DONGWOOK]
And then, people will be free
to move back to the island.
[BAEK YOONHO]
But that scream at the end.
I don't know.
[MIN BYUNG-GU]
What does it matter, man?
We just took down
the queen ant of Jeju Island!
Eunseok can rest in peace
'cause we avenged him!
[smirks]
[sighs]
[both chuckle]
[BAEK YOONHO]
I guess we did.
[alarm blaring]
Red alert, sir!
The ants are moving
back into the nest!
[GOTO RYUJI]
What?
[SUGIMOTO REIJI]
The signal lost effectiveness!
[GOTO RYUJI]
What's going on?
Give me the fastest
sitrep you can.
♪
A victory we all earned.
[gasps]
[shattering]
[CHOI JONG-IN]
My cage of fire was broken?
♪
What's going on?
We should've had plenty
of time to retreat!
[MIN BYUNG-GU] Yoonho was
right about that last scream.
You guys...
[MA DONGWOOK]
She was calling for help!
[CHA HAE-IN] Maybe,
but even if she was,
they can't get in.
Guildmaster Choi's
defense should hold.
[MIN BYUNG-GU]
Should hold?
[BAEK YOONHO]
Something's coming.
♪
[thumping]
[BAEK YOONHO]
What the hell is that thing?
♪
[groans]
[CHA HAE-IN]
What kind of beast could have
such a spine-chilling presence,
and suffocating smell?
That's...no ordinary ant!
[MA DONGWOOK]
There's no time to hesitate.
We need to take it out!
[thumping]
[gasps]
It walked right by us.
[wind howling]
[chewing]
♪
[growls]
[roaring]
♪
[gasps]
[grunting]
[thuds]
[MA DONGWOOK]
No! Miss Cha!
Hm!
Wrong move!
[shattering]
[growling]
♪
[groaning]
[growls]
[grunting]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[blood splashing]
♪
[LIM TAE-GYU]
You're finished!
He caught it mid-air!
[grunts]
♪
You surprised?
We've got a heck
of a healer with us!
[MIN BYUNG-GU]
Never been more thankful
for my Camouflage skill.
Conceals my presence
the same way Stealth does.
I can't move while using it,
but that's a non-issue
for a healer.
As long as I'm here,
my team won't go down!
[Ma Dongwook growls]
[gasps]
Ahh!
[grunts]
♪
[groans]
[gasps]
[MIN BYUNG-GU]
Is it perceptive enough
to see through Camouflage?
[BAEK YOONHO]
Byung-gu, no!
No!
[coughs]
♪
[BAEK YOONHO]
Byung-gu!
Run away, Yoonho.
Run away.
[blood splashing]
[roars]
[grunts]
[choking]
[squeaking]
[ANT KING]
Yoonho.
[gasps]
[ANT KING]
Run...
away.
Yoonho...
run.
Run away.
You sick son of a bitch!
[choking]
[ANT KING]
You are all weak...
and yet, you killed her.
You killed our queen.
Killing your soldiers...
is not enough.
Tell me...
where is your king?
-[trembling]
-[BAEK YOONHO] Our king?
♪
[ANT KING]
Outside. Yes.
A stronger one nears.
[sighs]
[coughs]
♪
Wait...
is he talking about Goto?
Well, whatever he meant,
we need to escape
while that thing's occupied!
[squealing]
[BAEK YOONHO]
Damn it!
These pests are relentless!
♪
[ISHIDA MARI]
I don't like this.
Something must be up.
First Charlie
stopped responding,
now Delta.
Interference, perhaps?
Although...
they should still
be within range.
Bravo, come in.
Go on ahead, sir.
[GOTO RYUJI] We've not heard
from Charlie or Delta.
-[GOTO RYUJI] You?
-[TAWATA KANAE] Negative.
[TAWATA KANAE] We lost
contact not too long ago.
Want us to investigate?
[GOTO RYUJI] No, we're
headed to their posts now.
Finish up on your end, then
meet at the rendezvous point.
[TAWATA KANAE]
Copy that.
[running footsteps]
[ISHIDA MARI]
But how?
[static buzzing]
[MATSUMOTO SHIGEO]
It's me.
Why aren't you checking in
according to schedule?
[GOTO RYUJI]
We've had casualties.
[MATSUMOTO SHIGEO]
Oh!
That's quite
unfortunate to hear.
I thought your orders were
to kill the evolved variants
to minimize the risk.
[GOTO RYUJI] And they
couldn't even handle that.
Such exacting standards.
Well...
I know you won't
have a problem,
so what's a death or two?
And our allies are dealing
with the queen as we speak?
[GOTO RYUJI]
Yes.
But the signal disruption
lost its effectiveness somehow,
and I confirmed the ants
are returning to the nest
to defend their leader.
[MATSUMOTO SHIGEO]
Hmm.
How likely is it that the
main strike team will survive?
The whole colony attacked.
Odds they'll live are zero.
[MATSUMOTO SHIGEO]
Sensational.
Despite fighting their hardest,
our Japanese hunters
were forced into
a temporary retreat
after our allies
were wiped out.
In honor of their sacrifice,
the second strike team
waiting at sea will close
the S-rank gate.
Japan will clear Jeju Island
and get the acclaim,
and a rival nation's military
will be decimated.
The timing's perfect.
Have all hunters withdraw
and rendezvous
with the secondary
strike force in the fleet.
[sighs]
[GOTO RYUJI]
Ten-four.
Orders from Chairman Matsumoto.
We're pulling out.
We'll come back
to collect the bodies at a--
[gasps]
-[thuds]
-Huh? Ishida!
-Focus.
-Huh?
Head to sea with Bravo
and prep for the next phase.
-I'll handle this.
-But--
You'll just be in my way
if you stay here.
[sighs]
-Go.
-Roger!
♪
[GOTO RYUJI]
Quite the remarkable aura.
[ANT KING]
Are you...
their king?
[GOTO RYUJI]
A talking ant.
Don't see that every day.
Yeah.
I'm king.
King of all hunters.
♪
What is this power?
Wait.
I've known something
like it before.
I felt it when...
[shattering]
♪
[explosions]
It might be time to crank up
the heat, Jong-in!
Do you feel the air in here?
This is as hot as it gets!
[BAEK YOONHO]
All of us are hurt pretty bad.
We can't fight back,
not with these wounds.
He's our last hope,
and he's fading.
♪
[explosion]
[squealing]
So, this is how it ends.
♪
[gasps]
[BAEK YOONHO]
These are...
But how did they get here?
Exchange.
♪